Psi Gamma Sorority and Alumnae Association, Inc.; Records ua801.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records, 1922-1997; 2
  - Series 1: Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Subject Files, 1922-1997 (with gaps); 2.1; 0.66 cubic ft.
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 12)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 13)
    - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 14)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 17)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 18)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 19)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 20)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 21)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 22)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 23)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 24)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 25)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 26)
    - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 27)
    - Officers and Board Members, 1988-1995 (Box 2 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 28)
  - Series 2: Psi Gamma Alumnae Association History Surveys, 1993-1995; 2.2; 0.4 cubic ft.
    This series consists of database print-outs and questionnaire forms relating to a survey conducted by the Alumnae Association to commemorate the University at Albany's sesquicentennial anniversary and the sorority's 95th anniversary. The database print-outs list the responses made by Psi Gamma Alumnae categorized by the questions taken from the questionnaires. The categories for the print-outs are: Advanced Degrees, Favorite Professor, Information on College Life, Information on Sorority Life, Memories of Sorority/College Life, Myskania and Purple and Gold Members, Personal History, Reason for Joining Psi Gamma, and Scholastic Honors. The questionnaires contain the responses used in the database print-outs as well as the phone numbers and addresses of the respondents.
    Questionnaires are alphabetized by alumnae member's maiden name.
    Arranged alphabetically by questionnaire titles and by the maiden names of the survey's respondents.
    - Questionnaire Responses: Advanced Degrees, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 1)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Favorite Professor, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 2)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Information on College Life, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 3)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Information on Sorority Life, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 4)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Memories of Sorority/College Life, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 5)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Myskania and Purple and Gold Members, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 6)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Personal History, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 7)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Reason for Joining Psi Gamma, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire Responses: Scholastic Honors, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 9)
    - Questionnaires: A-D, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 10)
    - Questionnaires: E-H, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 11)
    - Questionnaires: I-L, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 12)
    - Questionnaires: M-P, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 13)
    - Questionnaires: Q-Z, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 14)
  - Series 3: Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Beta Chapter Files, 1991-1995; 2.3; 0.16 cubic ft.
    This series consists of copies of Executive Board Minutes (1991-1992), general meeting minutes (1992-1994), correspondence (1991-1994), membership lists (1992-1995), officer lists (1992-1995), and alumnae lists (1993-1994). Important events documented in this series include the foundation of the sorority (1991), its recognition by Psi Gamma's Alpha Chapter in Albany (1991), the Beta Chapter's recognition by the Alumnae Association (1993), and its official incorporation (1994).
    - Alumnae Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 1)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1994 October (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 2)
    - Budgets, 1991; 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 3)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 4)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 6)
    - Membership Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 7)
    - Membership Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 8)
    - Membership Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Executive Board, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 10)
    - Minutes: General Meeting, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 11)
    - Minutes: General Meeting, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 12)
    - Officer Lists, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 13)
    - Pledge List, Undated (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 14)
    - President's Report, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 15)
    - Psi Gamma Sorority Traditions and Administration Forms, Undated (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 16)
    - Rush Recruitment Plan, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 17)
  - Series 4: Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Financial Records, 1987-1995; 2.4; 0.25 cubic ft.
    This series is composed of claim vouchers (1995), an Exempt Organization Certificate (1994), interest income tax forms (1988, 1992-1994), monthly bank statements (1987-1990), and a savings certificate passbook (1988-1995). Of particular importance is the state filing receipt of Amendments to Alumnae Association Certificate of Incorporation (1994) which allowed the association to act as the official sponsor of the Beta Chapter in Stony Brook.
    - Claim Vouchers, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 1)
    - Exempt Organization Certification, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 2)
    - Interest Income Tax Forms, 1988; 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 3)
    - Monthly Bank Statements, 1987 August-1990 March (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 4)
    - Savings Certificate Passbook, 1988-1995 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 5)
    - State Filing Receipt of Amendments to Alumnae Association Certificate of Incorporation, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records), Folder 6)